animatron.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Animatron

Pursuant to our Terms of Use, this document describes how we treat personal information related to your use of this website and the services offered on an through it (the “Service”), including information you provide when using it.

We expressly and strictly limit use of the Service to adults over 13 years of age or the age of majority in the individual’s jurisdiction, whichever is greater. Anyone under this age is strictly forbidden from using the Service. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained this age.

## Data Collected

_Browsing the Website._ You can use the search function, view articles, videos and pictures, and access other parts of the Service without having an account, in which case only your IP address, country of origin and other non-personal information about your computer or device (such as web requests, browser type, browser language, referring URL, operating system and date and time of requests) will be recorded for log file information, aggregated traffic information and in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content. If you have an account on the website and are logged in, the information may be associated with your account.

_Registering on the Website._ Registration of an account is required for using many parts of the Service, including saving your projects and using many other features. We request additional information at the time of your registration, including your name, email address and a password. Your IP address is recorded automatically. Some of this information may be used to provide you the Service and may become publicly available through your profile or through other use of the Service.

_Usage Information._ We may record information about your usage of the Service such as the videos you view, the frequency and size of data transfers and other statistics. If you have registered and are logged in, we may associate that information with your account.

_Uploaded Content._ Any personal information or content you voluntarily publicly disclose online, including animations, pictures, videos, comments and your profile page or any other User Submissions, becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others.

_Other Information._ You may have the ability to favorite content, make comments on content and engage in other social activities. Any such activities may be visible to the public.

_Correspondences._ We may keep a record of any correspondence between you and us.

_Cookies._ When you use the Service, we may send cookies to your computer to uniquely identify your browser session. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies.

## Data Usage

We may use your information to provide you with certain features and to create a personalized experience on the Service. We may also use that information to operate, maintain and improve features and functionality of the Service.

We may use your e-mail address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages. We may use your e-mail for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

We use cookies, web beacons and other information to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it on future visits, provide personalized content and information, monitor the effectiveness of the Service and monitor aggregate metrics such as the number of visitors and page views (including for use in monitoring visitors from affiliates). They may also be used to provide targeted advertising based on your country of origin and other personal information.

We may aggregate your personal information with personal information of other members and users, and disclose such information to advertisers and other third-parties for marketing and promotional purposes.

Your username may be displayed to other visitors of the Service alongside content on the Service in relation to your uploaded content and other similar features.

We may use your information to run promotions, contests, surveys and other features and events.

## Disclosures of Information

We may be required to release certain data to comply with legal obligations or in order to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. We may also release certain data to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users and others. This includes providing information to other companies or organizations like the police or governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against or prosecution of any illegal activity, whether or not it is identified in the Terms of Use.

If you upload any illegal material to the Service, or you are suspected of doing such, we may forward all available information to relevant authorities, including respective copyright owners, without any notice to you.

We may also share your information with third parties for the purposes of payment processing and any such information will also be subject to their privacy policies.

## Miscellaneous

If you have an account on the Service and have a password giving you access to certain parts of the Service, you are responsible for keeping the password confidential. Anyone else with your password may access your account and other personal information.

While we use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to secure your information, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information or content you transmit to us. Any information or content you transmit to us is done at your own risk.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

2 Seaport Lane, Suite 8C, 8th Floor, Seaport East   
Boston, MA 02210
